(Sheldon:)Leonard, what you're experiencing
is a classic Jungian crisis...
(Sheldon:)...in which the aging individual
mourns the loss...
...of the never-to-be-realized
ideal family unit.
(Leonard:)-Thank you, that's very comforting.
-That's not the comforting part.
(Leonard:)-It's not?
-No. No, the comforting part...
(Sheldon:)...is that the Germans have a term
for what you're feeling, "Weltschmerz."
(Sheldon:)It means the depression that arises
from comparing the world as it is...
(Sheldon:)...to a hypothetical idealized world.
(Leonard:)You're right, I do feel better.
Yeah, the Germans have always been
a comforting people.
(Sheldon:)Just remember, Leonard, where
your biological family has failed you...
(Sheldon:)...you always have me,
your surrogate family.
(Leonard:)You're my surrogate family?
(Sheldon:)If it's any consolation,
I'm not happy about it either. Good night.